{
  "apikey": "%PUT-YOUR-API-KEY-HERE%",
  "description": "This is simple calibration data used for testing purposes. Do not use it in production environment!",
  "copyright": "Copyright (C) 2238 by BanAN Technologies Inc.",
  "test-data": [
    {
      "question": "27 + 60",
      "answer": 87
    },
    {
      "question": "81 + 2",
      "answer": 83
    },
    {
      "question": "36 + 26",
      "answer": 62
    },
    {
      "question": "33 + 54",
      "answer": 87
    },
    {
      "question": "93 + 21",
      "answer": 114
    },
    {
      "question": "8 + 100",
      "answer": 108
    },
    {
      "question": "34 + 8",
      "answer": 42
    },
    {
      "question": "49 + 47",
      "answer": 96
    },
    {
      "question": "94 + 64",
      "answer": 158
    },
    {
      "question": "19 + 16",
      "answer": 35
    },
    {
      "question": "60 + 35",
      "answer": 95
    },
    {
      "question": "28 + 34",
      "answer": 62
    },
    {
      "question": "91 + 18",
      "answer": 109
    },
    {
      "question": "12 + 29",
      "answer": 41
    },
    {
      "question": "21 + 37",
      "answer": 58
    },
    {
      "question": "30 + 93",
      "answer": 123
    },
    {
      "question": "13 + 45",
      "answer": 58
    },
    {
      "question": "48 + 37",
      "answer": 85
    },
    {
      "question": "7 + 3",
      "answer": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "69 + 9",
      "answer": 78
    },
    {
      "question": "31 + 35",
      "answer": 66
    },
    {
      "question": "46 + 96",
      "answer": 142
    },
    {
      "question": "76 + 91",
      "answer": 167
    },
    {
      "question": "69 + 53",
      "answer": 122
    },
    {
      "question": "92 + 94",
      "answer": 186
    },
    {
      "question": "80 + 27",
      "answer": 107
    },
    {
      "question": "14 + 72",
      "answer": 86
    },
    {
      "question": "52 + 23",
      "answer": 75
    },
    {
      "question": "41 + 36",
      "answer": 77
    },
    {
      "question": "100 + 56",
      "answer": 156
    },
    {
      "question": "67 + 9",
      "answer": 76
    },
    {
      "question": "71 + 99",
      "answer": 170
    },
    {
      "question": "77 + 60",
      "answer": 137
    },
    {
      "question": "20 + 47",
      "answer": 67
    },
    {
      "question": "50 + 84",
      "answer": 134
    },
    {
      "question": "85 + 3",
      "answer": 88
    },
    {
      "question": "40 + 23",
      "answer": 63
    },
    {
      "question": "94 + 10",
      "answer": 104
    },
    {
      "question": "45 + 38",
      "answer": 83
    },
    {
      "question": "15 + 92",
      "answer": 107
    },
    {
      "question": "53 + 59",
      "answer": 112
    },
    {
      "question": "44 + 3",
      "answer": 47
    },
    {
      "question": "1 + 96",
      "answer": 97
    },
    {
      "question": "36 + 40",
      "answer": 76
    },
    {
      "question": "26 + 47",
      "answer": 73
    },
    {
      "question": "6 + 34",
      "answer": 40
    },
    {
      "question": "9 + 49",
      "answer": 58
    },
    {
      "question": "82 + 52",
      "answer": 134
    },
    {
      "question": "25 + 35",
      "answer": 60
    },
    {
      "question": "75 + 72",
      "answer": 147
    },
    {
      "question": "45 + 84",
      "answer": 129
    },
    {
      "question": "5 + 50",
      "answer": 55
    },
    {
      "question": "65 + 66",
      "answer": 131
    },
    {
      "question": "76 + 96",
      "answer": 172
    },
    {
      "question": "66 + 52",
      "answer": 118
    },
    {
      "question": "53 + 34",
      "answer": 87
    },
    {
      "question": "26 + 89",
      "answer": 115
    },
    {
      "question": "6 + 90",
      "answer": 96
    },
    {
      "question": "46 + 89",
      "answer": 135
    },
    {
      "question": "31 + 84",
      "answer": 115
    },
    {
      "question": "27 + 48",
      "answer": 75
    },
    {
      "question": "79 + 77",
      "answer": 156
    },
    {
      "question": "71 + 97",
      "answer": 168
    },
    {
      "question": "8 + 62",
      "answer": 70
    },
    {
      "question": "50 + 98",
      "answer": 148
    },
    {
      "question": "68 + 7",
      "answer": 75
    },
    {
      "question": "18 + 5",
      "answer": 23
    },
    {
      "question": "76 + 37",
      "answer": 113
    },
    {
      "question": "3 + 32",
      "answer": 35
    },
    {
      "question": "73 + 40",
      "answer": 113
    },
    {
      "question": "47 + 77",
      "answer": 124
    },
    {
      "question": "55 + 45",
      "answer": 100
    },
    {
      "question": "19 + 34",
      "answer": 53
    },
    {
      "question": "31 + 24",
      "answer": 55
    },
    {
      "question": "47 + 88",
      "answer": 135
    },
    {
      "question": "37 + 56",
      "answer": 93
    },
    {
      "question": "39 + 72",
      "answer": 111
    },
    {
      "question": "60 + 31",
      "answer": 91
    },
    {
      "question": "43 + 72",
      "answer": 115
    },
    {
      "question": "63 + 4",
      "answer": 67
    },
    {
      "question": "86 + 100",
      "answer": 186
    },
    {
      "question": "2 + 73",
      "answer": 75
    },
    {
      "question": "99 + 30",
      "answer": 129
    },
    {
      "question": "4 + 66",
      "answer": 70
    },
    {
      "question": "89 + 47",
      "answer": 136
    },
    {
      "question": "68 + 77",
      "answer": 145
    },
    {
      "question": "18 + 69",
      "answer": 87
    },
    {
      "question": "71 + 12",
      "answer": 83
    },
    {
      "question": "5 + 53",
      "answer": 58
    },
    {
      "question": "59 + 51",
      "answer": 110
    },
    {
      "question": "83 + 38",
      "answer": 121
    },
    {
      "question": "95 + 9",
      "answer": 104
    },
    {
      "question": "21 + 33",
      "answer": 54
    },
    {
      "question": "98 + 95",
      "answer": 193
    },
    {
      "question": "28 + 84",
      "answer": 112
    },
    {
      "question": "54 + 91",
      "answer": 145
    },
    {
      "question": "94 + 59",
      "answer": 153
    },
    {
      "question": "24 + 89",
      "answer": 113
    },
    {
      "question": "11 + 24",
      "answer": 35
    },
    {
      "question": "6 + 34",
      "answer": 40
    }
  ],
  "chunk": {
    "number": 8,
    "total": 22,
    "size": 100,
    "range": {
      "from": 700,
      "to": 800
    }
  }
}